export const pythonFunctionsAssignment = {
  title: 'Python Functions â€“ Assignment',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which keyword is mandatory in a Python function?',
      options: ['return', 'def', 'call', 'print'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is the default return value of a function?',
      options: ['0', 'False', 'None', 'Empty'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which allows a function to accept optional arguments?',
      options: [
        'Default parameters',
        'Return',
        'Loops',
        'Conditions',
      ],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'How do you call a function named test?',
      options: ['call test()', 'test()', 'run test', 'execute test'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Which is NOT a benefit of functions?',
      options: [
        'Code reuse',
        'Modularity',
        'Improved readability',
        'Increased redundancy',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which statement exits a function?',
      options: ['break', 'continue', 'return', 'exit'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Function arguments are separated by?',
      options: [';', ':', ',', '.'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which function returns multiple values?',
      options: [
        'Not possible',
        'Using tuple',
        'Using list only',
        'Using loop',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Functions help reduce?',
      options: ['Logic', 'Memory', 'Repetition', 'Errors only'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Functions are part of which concept?',
      options: [
        'Procedural programming',
        'Object-oriented programming',
        'Functional programming',
        'All of the above',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
  ],
}